Hello friends, welcome to my
channel Shatru Tech. Today in this video we will
see how we will do
third party insurance for two wheeler through ICICI Lombard General Insurance.
Okay, so stay tuned
to the video, let's start the video.
For this, go to your Google Chrome and
type here
Digital
Seva Portal.
After typing this, first a link will appear, click on it.
Here the people button will appear, click on people.
After that,
you have to
come to insurance here.
After that, you will come down here and see that there is
motor third party at the very end.
Click on it.
After clicking here, you will select
from whichever provider you want to get your insurance done.
I am going to do it through
ICICI Lombard here,
but I will
not do mine or yours. I want to do third party. The
third party is here, so
click on motor third party POS here.
Okay,
as soon as you click, an interface like this will
open. If you go through Google,
like I am doing this through CSC, then
I got its link here. You can also search it
in Google.  Even if you type ICICI Lombard General
Insurance, you will be
directed to this website. Okay, so here
I will select Two Wheeler Third Party,
after that you don't have to do anything, you have to
click on Get here. Okay,
like my insurance has lapsed, so
I am getting it done. If you
want to get a new one, then select this option.
Okay, so
I am renewing it or if my
insurance has lapsed, then I will select this second
option. Then here I have to click on Get Code.
Then it will go to the next page. Here you have to
enter your registration number.
Here I have entered the registration number.
You have to enter the vehicle number and
click on Get RTO Details.
After that, your vehicle
related details will open here. Okay,
here you can remove the
option which you want to remove from it. Okay, you
can remove it according to your retirement.
Okay,
here there is already a personal accident
cover, so you will advise on Yes. You
will click on No. On paying No, this will be
your personal accident cover of Rs. 375.  The
premium amount will be added to the premium,
okay, I don't have it,
okay, so I will click on the already holds personal
accident cover no and it will
show your premium amount here, you
can see the breakup here
how much has been charged for you, so this is only your
cover driver, this is 375 rupees,
your advisory charge is normal, the same will be applied,
now what you will do here is
click on proceed,
after clicking on proceed,
you will enter your customer details,
date of birth, after that enter the address here,
enter the pin code here,
after entering these, you will
select the city from here, you will
select the state here, the state
option is also not popping up, it is a bit slow, that
means the system is slow till here, you will enter the email ID, you will enter the
mobile number, the
PAN number option is
also not coming up,
okay, the statement has been shown here, okay, after
entering the details here in this way,
click here, then your nominee details
option will open here, you can click here  You
can enter the nominee details
in relation ship here, whatever relation you have,
you will enter it here,
after that you will click on generate proposal here,
your proposal number has been generated here, the
total premium amount will be shown to you here,
click on bin at 1271,
we
can see here your sale amount is
₹1271, 1205 will be detected from the wallet,
that is,
you can see in this,
you will get a benefit of about 64 in this, you will
validate it,
then you will be asked for wallet PIN number,
you will enter it
and click
here, you can see your calculation is done, in
this way
you
can do third party insurance for your two wheeler, okay, all your
details are given here, name,
insurance, RTO details, till when it will be valid, you
can see everything of yours in this,
you will come to the second page,
here the
policy issue date is September 23,
2021, okay
and this is your period insurance, yours is
valid from 24th to 23rd September 2022  So friends, in this way
you
can get third party insurance for your two wheeler. Okay,
friends, I hope you liked this video.
If you liked the video, then
like the video and those who are new to my channel,
please subscribe to my channel and
press the bell icon
for video notifications.
Jai Hind, Jai Bharat.